{
    "id": "7758f4246ee2492ea9d34acdab49ed96",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "………………….. she was a foreigner made it difficult for her to get a job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "That",
                "The fact that"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I will come with you …………………. your wife doesn’t mind.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so that",
                "providing that"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am very …………………… for all your help.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "thankful",
                "grateful",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is thinking ………………….. her job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to quit",
                "of quitting"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………. a terrorist.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "thought",
                "was thought to be"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She spent ………………… browsing through the catalogue.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ten happy minutes",
                "happy ten minutes",
                "a happy ten minutes"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I am very …………………. in the lesson.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "interesting",
                "interested"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I mean ………………….. what is going on.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to find out",
                "finding out"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You should always check the oil before ………………….. the car.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "starting",
                "to start"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I am tired ………………… to this.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to listen",
                "of listening"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}